If the sky clears, lalala we’ll sing
空が晴れたら   ラララ歌おう
a song about our memories together
おそろいの想い出の歌
Surely if we’re apart our feelings will be connected
きっと離れても  繋がる気持ち
by a special magic
スペシャルな魔法
A memory from my heart
ココロのメモリーいっぱい
overflowing me as I’m smiling and crying
あふれてる笑顔泣き顔
Hiding my face from everybody
誰にも見せない顔
All of these treasured things
すべてが宝物
Beyond the horizon, a new road has begun
地平線の彼方へ  駆け出した道
I want to take any wind towards it!
どんな風も  受け止めたいよ
The important winds shining too for a second
一秒がキラめいて  大切すぎて
All the while, it would be good to stay
ずっと ずーっと  このままがいい
Really, we grew a little,
ほんのちょっと伸びた背
Had days that we were proud of
自慢しあった日々
and days that we were nearly crying from laughter
涙がでるほど笑ったこと
All of these irreplaceable memories with friends
すべてがかけがえのない想い出たち
Let's hum an unending song
終わらない歌を  口ずさもう
because we're a group
仲間だから
As we disappear together, a rainbow of happiness
一瞬で消えちゃう  しあわせの虹
begins to form before us
気づけるように前向いて行こう
Happy, fun, we meet all divided
嬉しい楽しい  全部分け合える
in a good relationship
関係っていいね
Talking casually,
なにげないおしゃべり
while blowing soap bubbles during an uncertain time
しゃぼん玉みたいな時間
Still, I’m not scared
まだ壊したくない
But now, I don’t want to go!
でも...もう行かなきゃ
Hold your head up high, with a blossoming smile
顔を上げてとびっきり  笑顔咲かせて
Try to look back on small moments like now
ちっちゃいなりに  振り向かせよう
Let dream balloons float towards the sky
膨らんだ夢のバルーン  放つ大空
Surely they will, here in this promised place
きっとここが  約束の場所
We liked the same things
好きなことは好き
We also had moments where we fought,
喧嘩もできちゃう
only over little things
それくらい近くにいたよね
But we’re opening a new door together
一緒に新しい扉を開けて
talking about dreams that will come true
語り合った夢  叶えに行こう
as a group
仲間だから
Beyond the horizon, a new road has begun
地平線の彼方へ  駆け出した道
I want to take any wind towards it!
どんな風も  受け止めたいよ
The important ones shining too for a second
一秒がキラめいて  大切すぎて
All the while, it would be good to stay
ずっと ずーっと  このままがいい
We said “bye” and shook hands
じゃあね,  と手を振った
We cried a bit
ちょっぴり泣けちゃった
We can not go back through the door after this day
戻れない扉を開けた日
Surely some day from now on we will be shining
その先のキラキラをいつかきっと
and we'll gather here and meet again
持ち寄って  ここでまた会おうね
as a group
仲間だから